Submarines
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Submarines, 2.1.3.1.3.1
  - Submarines: Illustrations, undated; 13 (Box 1510)
    - [p. 378 of "Der Kreig 1914-19 in Wort und Bild" Photographed + retouched Used in 2nd installment (W.W. May '28) "Raiders of the Deep Sinking of the British Battleship "Majestic" Torpedoed by Otto von Hersin off Gallipoli May 27, 1915], 18
    - Verso: p. 378 of "Der Kreig 1914-19 in Wort und Bild" Photographed + retouched Used in 2nd installment (W.W. May '28) "Raiders of the Deep Sinking of the British Battleship "Majestic" Torpedoed by Otto von Hersin off Gallipoli May 27, 1915, 18-verso
    - [Destroyer returning to shore, soldiers cheering on dock], 19
    - [Sinking of Unarmed Fishermen off Cape Cod by George E. Browne], 20
    - Verso: Sinking of Unarmed Fishermen off Cape Cod by George E. Browne, 20-verso
    - [Aerial view of harbor or submarine base], 21
    - [Sinking of Hospitral Ship by Charles Hopkinson], 22
    - Verso: Sinking of Hospitral Ship by Charles Hopkinson, 22-verso
  - Submarines: Italy, circa 1914 - 1918; 14 (Box 1510)
    - [Royal Italian Sub. Jalea], 1
    - Verso: Royal Italian Sub. Jalea, 1-verso
    - [Italian Sub. Type N], 2
    - Verso: Italian Sub. Type N, 2-verso
    - [Italian sub. Returning from an expedition (a mission)], 3
    - Verso: Italian sub. Returning from an expedition (a mission), 3-verso
    - [Italian coastal sub. Type A], 4
    - Verso: Italian coastal sub. Type A, 4-verso
    - [Commander Giovanni of the submarine Jalea], 5
    - Verso: Commander Giovanni of the submarine Jalea, 5-verso
    - [Capt of Corvette Carlo de Greco commander of the Italian sub Nereide, torpedoed by Com. von Trapp], 6
    - Verso: Capt of Corvette Carlo de Greco commander of the Italian sub Nereide, torpedoed by Com. von Trapp, 6-verso
    - [Italian sub Balilla], 7
    - Verso: Italian sub Balilla, 7-verso
    - [Italian sub Nereide torpedoed and destroyed by the Austrian Comm. Von Trapp in U-5], 8
    - Verso: Italian sub Nereide torpedoed and destroyed by the Austrian Comm. Von Trapp in U-5, 8-verso
    - [Ensign (Lieut. of The ship) Com. O'Byrne, John in command of the French submarine Curie The Curie was captured by the Austrians as it tried to slip into Pola(?) and torpedo the battleship there. It was raised and refitted and became the Austrian U-4 under Com. von Trapp], 9
    - Verso: Ensign (Lieut. of The ship) Com. O'Byrne, John in command of the French submarine Curie The Curie was captured by the Austrians as it tried to slip into Pola[?] and torpedo the battleship there. It was raised and refitted and became the Austrian U-4 under Com. von Trapp, 9-verso
    - [U 12 Austrian Submarine work in front of Venice and recuperated by the Italian navy], 10
    - Verso: U 12 Austrian Submarine work in front of Venice and recuperated by the Italian navy, 10-verso
    - [U12, Austrian Sub. Sank off Venetian coast and raised (RECUPERATED-SO TO SPEAK) by the Italian Navy.], 11
    - Verso: U12, Austrian Sub. Sank off Venetian coast and raised (RECUPERATED-SO TO SPEAK) by the Italian Navy., 11-verso
    - [Command Farinata Degli Uberti commanding the Italian submarine Balilla], 12
    - Verso: Command Farinata Degli Uberti commanding the Italian submarine Balilla, 12-verso
    - [Italian sub. for coast protection ready to put to sea], 13
    - Verso: Italian sub. for coast protection ready to put to sea, 13-verso
    - [UC 12 Sub. Sank of Taranto and resurrected [Raised(Recuperated-so to speak)] by the Italian Navy.], 14
    - Verso: UC 12 Sub. Sank of Taranto and resurrected [Raised(Recuperated-so to speak)] by the Italian Navy., 14-verso
    - [Italian Sub Pietro Micca], 15
    - Verso: Italian Sub Pietro Micca, 15-verso
    - [Italian Sub. Type F.], 16
    - Verso: Italian Sub. Type F., 16-verso
    - [Half submerged sub (Returning of an Italian sub. To Brindisi after her mission)], 17
    - Verso: Half submerged sub (Returning of an Italian sub. To Brindisi after her mission), 17-verso
    - [Load of torpedo's on board an Italian sub], 18
    - Verso: Load of torpedo's on board an Italian sub, 18-verso
    - [Austrian Sub. U12 sank near Venice and recuperated (raised) by the Italians.], 19
    - Verso: Austrian Sub. U12 sank near Venice and recuperated (raised) by the Italians., 19-verso
  - Submarines: Captain Waldemar Kophamel, circa 1914 - 1918; 15 (Box 1510)
    - [hegatter [?] Kapitan Waldemar Kophamel[?] U35 U151 U140], 1
    - Verso: hegatter [?] Kapitan Waldemar Kophamel[?] U35 U151 U140, 1-verso
    - [Captain Kophamel examining ruins on deck of the U151 after collision with destroyer (Kophamel)], 2
    - Verso: Captain Kophamel examining ruins on deck of the U151 after collision with destroyer (Kophamel), 2-verso
    - [Norwegian steamer Johann Myelde fastened to U151 while her cargo of copper is transferred to hold of submarine. (Kophamel)], 3
    - Verso: Norwegian steamer Johann Myelde fastened to U151 while her cargo of copper is transferred to hold of submarine. (Kophamel), 3-verso
    - [Officers in "undress" uniform (Kophamel story)], 4
    - Verso: Officers in "undress" uniform (Kophamel story), 4-verso
    - [Gun crew I don't know which sub (Kophamel)], 5
    - Verso: Gun crew I don't know which sub (Kophamel), 5-verso
  - Commander Korner, circa 1914 - 1918; 16 (Box 1510)
    - [S.S Chilier sunk by U-151], 1
    - Verso: S.S Chilier sunk by U-151, 1-verso
    - [Norwegian S.S. "Vinland" in sinking situation sunk 5.6.1918 by U-151], 2
    - Verso: Norwegian S.S. "Vinland" in sinking situation sunk 5.6.1918 by U-151, 2-verso
    - [S.S. "Vinland" sinking U-151], 3
    - Verso: S.S. "Vinland" sinking U-151, 3-verso
    - Note: Korner pictures, save for the next books, 4
  Box 1511
- Submarines, 2.1.3.1.3.1
  - Submarines: T. L. Seith photographs, circa 1914 - 1929; 1 (Box 1511)
    - [New York May 30 18], 1
    - Verso: New York May 30 18, 1-verso
    - [Sailors in boats waiting to board ship], 2
    - [ of the crew of the Alan[?] Matheo[?] Sunk bys us in a collision on on April 23 1918 12:30 A.M.], 3
    - Verso: of the crew of the Alan[?] Matheo[?] Sunk bys us in a collision on on April 23 1918 12:30 A.M., 3-verso
    - [Three sailors staring at camera], 4
    - Note: Survivors of the British streamer Clan Matheson, sunk in collision with U.S.S. Western Front while zig-zagging through war zone. May 23 1918 1:30 A.M., 5
    - Types of guns manned by Naval Armed Guard aboard transports and merhcant ships carrying munitions and supplies to France, 6
    - Note: Types of guns manned by Naval Armed Guard aboard transports and merhcant ships carrying munitions and supplies to France, 7
    - [Sailors gathered around apparatus on deck of ship], 8
    - [Malimousan(?)-death Parsons, "Spike" (Killed) Sheridan "Spud" Oswego Calwell"Melle" Chicago Lakin (Killed) Melvin "Salty" (wounded) Woolslare(?) (Pittsburg) Ofenback(?)-Chicago Haney-New Orleans Malcomson (slightly wounded) Sware(?) (died of wound) Osis, Chicago Sarmpk(?) Erie Pa. Smith "Shot accidently"], 9
    - [Malimousan[?]-death Parsons, "Spike" (Killed) Sheridan "Spud" Oswego Calwell"Melle" Chicago Lakin (Killed) Melvin "Salty" (wounded) Woolslare[?] (Pittsburg) Ofenback[?]-Chicago Haney-New Orleans Malcomson (slightly wounded) Sware[?] (died of wound) Osis, Chicago Sarmpk[?] Erie Pa. Smith "Shot accidently", 9-verso
    - A French derigible on patrol duty off the coast of France, 10
    - Note: A French derigible on patrol duty off the coast of France, 11
    - S. S. Luckenback after a 5 hour battle with a German submarine. This was the longest naval battle during the war in which the American Navy participated, 12
    - Note: S. S. Luckenback after a 5 hour battle with a German submarine. This was the longest naval battle during the war in which the American Navy participated, 13
    - A captured German submarine in the mouth of the Gironde River, France., 14
    - Note: A captured German submarine in the mouth of the Gironde River, France., 15
    - [Taken Nov. 19, 1917 Shelled by J.L. Luckenback + U.S. Fanning. Surrendered at 160 miles off Queenstown], 16
    - Verso: Taken Nov. 19, 1917 Shelled by J.L. Luckenback + U.S. Fanning. Surrendered at 160 miles off Queenstown, 16-verso
    - [Conning tower of sub. 11-19-17 U.S.S. Fanning taking off prisoners. 6 P.M. 150 miles off Queenstown Ireland.], 17
    - Verso: Conning tower of sub. 11-19-17 U.S.S. Fanning taking off prisoners. 6 P.M. 150 miles off Queenstown Ireland., 17-verso
    - U-58 captured November 19 1929 off Queenstown Ireland, 18
    - Verso: 11-19-17 U-58 attacked by steamer uchkenback and U.S.S. Fanning Surrendered at 150 mile off Queenstown Ireland., 18-verso
    - Note: U-58 captured November 19 1929 off Queenstown Ireland, 19
    - Envelope, 20
  - Submarines: Submarines, circa 1914 - 1918; 2 (Box 1511)
    - [The White Ensign ruses over the German Imperial war flag, surrender of U-boats at Harwich.], 1
    - Verso: The White Ensign ruses over the German Imperial war flag, surrender of U-boats at Harwich., 1-verso
    - [British battleship Britannia, torpedoed in [?] only 2 days before armstice by Henrich Kukat], 2
    - Verso: British battleship Britannia, torpedoed in [?] only 2 days before armstice by Henrich Kukat, 2-verso
    - [Listened[?] thru hydrophone for a German submarine], 3
    - Verso: Listened[?] thru hydrophone for a German submarine, 3-verso
    - [Part 1 Reel 1 Commander of U-35 comes on board as U-boat is ready to cast loose for tryer[?]], 4
    - Verso: Part 1 Reel 1 Commander of U-35 comes on board as U-boat is ready to cast loose for tryer[?], 4-verso
    - [Part 8 Reel 2 The armed Italian steamship "Stromboli"], 5
    - Verso: Part 8 Reel 2 The armed Italian steamship "Stromboli", 5-verso
    - [The U-35 detains a sailing ship while its papers are examined.], 6
    - Verso: The U-35 detains a sailing ship while its papers are examined., 6-verso
    - [U-35 Bananas from sunken steamer.], 7
    - Verso: U-35 Bananas from sunken steamer., 7-verso
    - [Part 8 Reel 2 The armed Italian steamship "Stromboli"], 8
    - Verso: Part 8 Reel 2 The armed Italian steamship "Stromboli", 8-verso
    - [Part 8 Reel 2 The armed Italian steamship "Stromboli"], 9
    - Verso: Part 8 Reel 2 The armed Italian steamship "Stromboli", 9-verso
    - [A U-boat coming into port in the Bay of Cattaro(?)], 10
    - Verso: A U-boat coming into port in the Bay of Cattaro[?], 10-verso
    - [The second officer of the U35 does a bit of laundry on deck.], 11
    - Verso: The second officer of the U35 does a bit of laundry on deck., 11-verso
    - [Part 1 Reel 3 Running on the surface in a heavy sea. The U-35], 12
    - Verso: Part 1 Reel 3 Running on the surface in a heavy sea. The U-35, 12-verso
    - [Part 3 Reel 2 The boat of the Asuarca[?] (neutral Spanish steamer) comes alongside to prove the ships's paper. On finding that cargo was not for enemy ship was allowed to proceed.], 13
    - Verso: Part 3 Reel 2 The boat of the Asuarca[?] (neutral Spanish steamer) comes alongside to prove the ships's paper. On finding that cargo was not for enemy ship was allowed to proceed., 13-verso
    - [Part 1 Reel 1 U-35 At Wilhlemshaven, commander comes on board as U-35 is ready to leave port.], 14
    - Verso: Part 1 Reel 1 U-35 At Wilhlemshaven, commander comes on board as U-35 is ready to leave port., 14-verso
    - [?], 15
    - Verso: ?, 15-verso
    - [Part 6 Reel 2 Boat from the neutral Spanish steamer Asuarca to prove ship's papers.], 16
    - Verso: Part 6 Reel 2 Boat from the neutral Spanish steamer Asuarca to prove ship's papers., 16-verso
    - [Part 4 Reel 2 The English schooner "Miss Morris" is stopped by the U-35], 17
    - Verso: Part 4 Reel 2 The English schooner "Miss Morris" is stopped by the U-35, 17-verso
    - [Part 4 Reel 2 The English schooner "Miss Morris" is stopped by the U-35], 18
    - Verso: Part 4 Reel 2 The English schooner "Miss Morris" is stopped by the U-35, 18-verso
    - [Part 4 Reel 2 The English schooner "Miss Morris" is stopped by the U-35 and her crew made to leave the ship.], 19
    - Verso: Part 4 Reel 2 The English schooner "Miss Morris" is stopped by the U-35 and her crew made to leave the ship., 19-verso
    - [Part 4 Reel 2 The English schooner "Miss Morris" is stopped by the U-35], 20
    - Verso: Part 4 Reel 2 The English schooner "Miss Morris" is stopped by the U-35, 20-verso
    - [Part 4 Reel 2 The English schooner "Miss Morris" is stopped and crew made to leave the ship.], 21
    - Verso: Part 4 Reel 2 The English schooner "Miss Morris" is stopped and crew made to leave the ship., 21-verso
    - [Caption: "U 35" im Hafen von Cartagena], 22
    - [Part 1 Reel 2 The commander (of the U-35) sets the course and the helmsman shoots the sun to find the position of the U-boat.], 23
    - Verso: Part 1 Reel 2 The commander (of the U-35) sets the course and the helmsman shoots the sun to find the position of the U-boat., 23-verso
    - [Norwegian sailor sunk by von Spiegel in U-93], 24
    - Verso: Norwegian sailor sunk by von Spiegel in U-93, 24-verso
    - [Going down], 25
    - Verso: Going down, 25-verso
    - [Italian sailing ship stopped by U-35], 26
    - Verso: Italian sailing ship stopped by U-35, 26-verso
    - [A conning tower I don't know which U-boat.], 27
    - Verso: A conning tower I don't know which U-boat., 27-verso
    - [View of dining room, chandelier hanging over table], 28
    - Verso: German officers dining room in Bruges., 28-verso
    - [Going Down: Sunk by Von Arnauld(?) aboard the U-35.], 29
    - Verso: Going Down: Sunk by Von Arnauld[?] aboard the U-35., 29-verso
    - [Above the stern of the steamer you may see the explosion of a shell. from U-151], 30
    - Verso: Above the stern of the steamer you may see the explosion of a shell. from U-151, 30-verso
    - [English ship-torpedoed-off French coast about-about July 1918-USS Harvard standing by.], 31
    - Verso: English ship-torpedoed-off French coast about-about July 1918-USS Harvard standing by., 31-verso
    - [Interior of German U boat], 32
    - Verso: Interior of German U boat, 32-verso
    - [Comm. Gustav Awberger[?] of the U-68. The only submarine sunk by American destroyers.], 33
    - Verso: Comm. Gustav Awberger[?] of the U-68. The only submarine sunk by American destroyers., 33-verso
    - [Torpedoed by a German submarine Photo taken by the Germans], 34
    - Verso: Torpedoed by a German submarine Photo taken by the Germans, 34-verso
    - [German subs at Zeebruge Branches on top were used as Camouflage], 35
    - Verso: German subs at Zeebruge Branches on top were used as Camouflage, 35-verso
    - [Koerner(?)], 36
    - Verso: Koerner[?], 36-verso
    - [This is U-35], 37
    - Verso: This is U-35, 37-verso
    - [U-35 (indecipherable text)], 38
    - Verso: U-35 (indecipherable text), 38-verso
    - [U 35 + ship sunk by gunfire after crew had taken to lifeboat], 39
    - Verso: U 35 + ship sunk by gunfire after crew had taken to lifeboat, 39-verso
    - [Part 1 Reel 3 Deck gun of U-35 in action], 40
    - Verso: Part 1 Reel 3 Deck gun of U-35 in action, 40-verso
    - [New U-boat from Germania wharf at Kiel leaving Helgoland], 41
    - Verso: New U-boat from Germania wharf at Kiel leaving Helgoland, 41-verso
    - [no description], 42
    - Verso, 43
    - [Picture of three ships out at sea], 43-verso
    - [Portrait of German naval officer, Captain lieutenant Derfing(?)], 44
    - Verso, 44-verso
  - Submarines: Submarines, circa 1914 - 1918; 3 (Box 1511)
    - German merchant super-submarine Deutschland as she started on her perilous dash to sea where hostile cruisers lie in wait, 1
    - Note: German merchant super-submarine Deutschland as she started on her perilous dash to sea where hostile cruisers lie in wait, 2
    - [Shell exploding], 3
    - Verso:Shell exploding, 3-verso
    - [Tower of the U-19, Back to port after a long trip.], 4
    - Verso: Tower of the U-19, Back to port after a long trip., 4-verso
    - [Manning a gun on a U.S. submarine chase], 5
    - Verso: Manning a gun on a U.S. submarine chase, 5-verso
    - [German naval men awaiting to be transfered to another ship after surrendered to the Allied Fleet], 6
    - Verso: German naval men awaiting to be transfered to another ship after surrendered to the Allied Fleet, 6-verso
    - [SURRENDER OF THE GERMAN FLEET. The dejected attitude of the Germans when a British officer boarded their submarine off Harwich yesterday (Thursday).], 7
    - Verso: SURRENDER OF THE GERMAN FLEET. The dejected attitude of the Germans when a British officer boarded their submarine off Harwich yesterday (Thursday)., 7-verso
    - [British Marine Exhibit], 8
    - Verso: British Marine Exhibit, 8-verso
    - [British Marine Exhibit], 9
    - Verso: British Marine Exhibit, 9-verso
    - [Part 3 Reel 1 Das Schiff erh lt gun Beschleuvegung der Sinkers Schusse in die Wasserlinie(?)], 10
    - Verso: Part 3 Reel 1 Das Schiff erh lt gun Beschleuvegung der Sinkers Schusse in die Wasserlinie[?], 10-verso
    - [Photo shows the Merchan Ship Mongolia, which is said to have sunk a German submarine.], 11
    - Verso: Photo shows the Merchan Ship Mongolia, which is said to have sunk a German submarine., 11-verso
    - [Submarine submerging at Berehaven. War picture. U.S. sub. In service on other side. Obsolete AL type.], 12
    - Verso: Submarine submerging at Berehaven. War picture. U.S. sub. In service on other side. Obsolete AL type., 12-verso
    - [Part 3 Reel 1 U-35], 13
    - Verso: Part 3 Reel 1 U-35, 13-verso
    - [(Duplicate - other print is better) Photograph from Johannes Spiers, commander of the U-9 in 1915-16. Sinking of an English fish steamer on Dogger Bank.], 14
    - Verso: (Duplicate - other print is better) Photograph from Johannes Spiers, commander of the U-9 in 1915-16. Sinking of an English fish steamer on Dogger Bank., 14-verso
    - [Submarine Mar 17 W.W.], 15
    - Verso: Submarine Mar 17 W.W., 15-verso
    - [German submarine (?) old Germania type], 16
    - Verso: German submarine [?] old Germania type, 16-verso
    - [Near end of Reel 3 - Part of crew on deck of U-35 at sunset Picture taken against setting sun.], 17
    - Verso: Near end of Reel 3 - Part of crew on deck of U-35 at sunset Picture taken against setting sun., 17-verso
    - [Passing friendly war ships on way to sea from naval base-presumably Wilhemshaven.], 18
    - Verso: Passing friendly war ships on way to sea from naval base-presumably Wilhemshaven., 18-verso
    - [Part 3 Reel 1 U-35 Deck gun], 19
    - Verso: Part 3 Reel 1 U-35 Deck gun, 19-verso
    - [Caption: THE BOGIE OF THE U-BOATS A depth bomb dropped by an American torpedo boat destroyer explodes and distrubrs tons of sos water in a neighborhood suspected of harboring a U-boat. Dozens submarines have met their fate from those bombs.], 20
    - [Part 5 Reel 2 Sailing vessel sunk by U-35 "Miss Morris" English schooner], 21
    - Verso: Part 5 Reel 2 Sailing vessel sunk by U-35 "Miss Morris" English schooner, 21-verso
    - [Submarine Oct. 16 star W.W.], 22
    - Verso: Submarine Oct. 16 star W.W., 22-verso
    - [No. 109 Letters from home and cigarette passed around], 23
    - Verso: No. 109 Letters from home and cigarette passed around, 23-verso
    - [letter and cigarettes all round return home from trip U-35], 24
    - Verso: letter and cigarettes all round return home from trip U-35, 24-verso
    - [Part 3 Reel 1 U-35 Deck gun in action], 25
    - Verso: Part 3 Reel 1 U-35 Deck gun in action, 25-verso
    - [Writing a radio message See picture No 100 for message. Commander von Armauld(?) on U-35], 26
    - Verso: Writing a radio message See picture No 100 for message. Commander von Armauld[?] on U-35, 26-verso
    - [Prisoners of War Five English commanders of ships overtaken and sunk, walking in the morning on the deck of the U-35.], 27
    - Verso: Prisoners of War Five English commanders of ships overtaken and sunk, walking in the morning on the deck of the U-35., 27-verso
    - [The Commander of the U-35 looks over Lloyd's Register to strike off name of latest victim.], 28
    - Verso: The Commander of the U-35 looks over Lloyd's Register to strike off name of latest victim., 28-verso
    - [Part 4 Reel 1 From U-35 film], 29
    - Verso: Part 4 Reel 1 From U-35 film, 29-verso
    - [Part 4 Reel 1 U-35], 30
    - Verso: Part 4 Reel 1 U-35, 30-verso
    - [Part 4 Reel 1], 31
    - Verso: Part 4 Reel 1, 31-verso
    - [Part 4 Reel 1 armed English steamer "Parkgate," 3232 tons, of the English navy, from Malta to Gibraltar; after long battle the U-35 stopped the Parkgate.], 32
    - Verso: Part 4 Reel 1 armed English steamer "Parkgate," 3232 tons, of the English navy, from Malta to Gibraltar; after long battle the U-35 stopped the Parkgate., 32-verso
    - [Part 4 Reel 1], 33
    - Verso: Part 4 Reel 1, 33-verso
    - [Part 4 Reel 1], 34
    - Verso: Part 4 Reel 1, 34-verso
    - [Part 3 Reel 1], 35
    - Verso: Part 3 Reel 1, 35-verso
    - [Part 3 Reel 1 "Parkgate"], 36
    - Verso: Part 3 Reel 1 "Parkgate", 36-verso
  - Submarines: Submarines, circa 1914 - 1918; 4 (Box 1511)
    - [Submarine somewhere in the Atlantic Making for theyr(sic) prey], 1
    - Verso: Submarine somewhere in the Atlantic Making for theyr(sic) prey, 1-verso
    - [U-35 at Wilhelmshaven], 2
    - Verso: U-35 at Wilhelmshaven, 2-verso
    - [U-35 returns home from successful raid Naval base; Wilhelmshaven Date: probably summer 1917], 3
    - Verso: U-35 returns home from successful raid Naval base; Wilhelmshaven Date: probably summer 1917, 3-verso
    - [Unidentified German warship passed on homeward trip of U-35. Evidently crew of German battleship cheering U-35 passing.], 4
    - Verso: Unidentified German warship passed on homeward trip of U-35. Evidently crew of German battleship cheering U-35 passing., 4-verso
    - [Part 2 Reel 2 Signal from sinking ship "Send the life boats"], 5
    - Verso: Part 2 Reel 2 Signal from sinking ship "Send the life boats", 5-verso
    - [Part 2 Reel 2 Cleaning deck gun of U-35 during good weather at sea.], 6
    - Verso: Part 2 Reel 2 Cleaning deck gun of U-35 during good weather at sea., 6-verso
    - [Part 2 Reel 2 Cleaning of Deck Gun of German submarine U-35 at sea during good weather.], 7
    - Verso: Part 2 Reel 2 Cleaning of Deck Gun of German submarine U-35 at sea during good weather., 7-verso
    - [Part 6 Reel 3. Not identified by caption. Evidently an officer from captured ship reporting to U-35 commander], 8
    - Verso: Part 6 Reel 3. Not identified by caption. Evidently an officer from captured ship reporting to U-35 commander, 8-verso
    - [Commander of the U-35 in conning tower.], 9
    - Verso: Commander of the U-35 in conning tower., 9-verso
    - [P-5 Reel 2 Sailing vessel sunk by U-35 "Miss Morris," English schooner], 10
    - Verso: P-5 Reel 2 Sailing vessel sunk by U-35 "Miss Morris," English schooner, 10-verso
    - [Part 5 Reel 2 Sailing vessel sunk by U-35 "Miss Morris," English schooner], 11
    - Verso: Part 5 Reel 2 Sailing vessel sunk by U-35 "Miss Morris," English schooner, 11-verso
    - [Part 5 Reel 2 Sailing vessel sunk by U-35 "Miss Morris," English schooner], 12
    - Verso: Part 5 Reel 2 Sailing vessel sunk by U-35 "Miss Morris," English schooner, 12-verso
    - [P-5 Reel 2 Sailing vessel sunk by U-35 "Miss Morris," English schooner], 13
    - Verso: P-5 Reel 2 Sailing vessel sunk by U-35 "Miss Morris," English schooner, 13-verso
    - [Part 5 Reel 2 Sailing vessel sunk by U-35 "Miss Morris," English schooner], 14
    - Verso: Part 5 Reel 2 Sailing vessel sunk by U-35 "Miss Morris," English schooner, 14-verso
    - [Part 6 Reel 3, U-35 exploits Store Film Library U-35 commanded by von Aswauld], 15
    - Verso: Part 6 Reel 3, U-35 exploits Store Film Library U-35 commanded by von Aswauld, 15-verso